<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Codingo - Ethical Hacking and Bug Bounty Advice</title><link>http://codingo.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Codingo - Ethical Hacking and Bug Bounty Advice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 23:42:04 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://codingo.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributing to Github for Information Security Professionals</title><link>http://codingo.com/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 23:42:04 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://codingo.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Every Month if Hacktoberfest, which, if you’re not already familiar with is an event run by Digital Ocean to reward open source contributions with swag (normally a t-shirt and stickers). All in all, it’s a very well received event that provides the perfect time to jump into open source, if you haven’t already.
The intention of this guide is to arm you with the knowledge of how you can get involved, even if you’re not entirely familiar with programming, or if you are, and you want a reference point for “how to github” - I’m aiming for this to land with both&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Wallets: What are the differences between them?</title><link>http://codingo.com/posts/2013-01-02-bitcoin-wallet-differences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 17:01:58 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://codingo.com/posts/2013-01-02-bitcoin-wallet-differences/</guid><description>Satoshi Nakamoto first published their paper on Bitcoin back in 2009, but it didn’t reach real mainstream popularity until recently. Only the users who understand the highly technical mechanics of Bitcoin invested their time in the technology during 2009-13 intermission period. In February of 2013 Bitcoin, and soon cryptocurrencies in general, finally entered the public consciousness. Despite being a four year old technology, many of the core features of the Bitcoin protocol were not polished in any capacity, let alone ready for mass public consumption.</description></item></channel></rss>